or anything else then please do like just chip in and raise your hand or shout
out if you've got
a question or something to say because you know we can all learn from each
other can't we?
Um and yeah maybe at the end we can we can all go around and say you know a
little bit about
how we felt if there's anything we've learned or if there's any tips we've got
or anything else.
Um so yeah shall we shall we go ahead then Jade you want to start? Yes of
course okay
okay then so we're coming full time
getting started okay so um some of these points actually we're from Lorna you
asked for us to
cover some of these things so here they are and so first of all you've got to
have the confidence
to start in yourself and in the job so obviously with webcombing you have the
days where you do
really amazing and you feel so confident because you know like I have all these
people complimenting
you and paying you loads of money just to speak to you and then your confidence
grows but then
you also have the days where you're not so busy so in those days we need to
remind ourselves to
like not let that knock our confidence and and you know don't let that be
reflection on us because
it's not it never is when we're not busy it's never ever reflection on on us um
but now for
question what is a good average day roughly in credit and I think that really
does depend on
how long you're on there for and to be honest like it all depends on the
individual but I
personally would be happy with like if I'm doing it full time maybe like two to
four hundred
credits would be a nice day I would say yeah but it's one of them it's hard to
say because maybe
you're going to have a day and make a lot more you know what I mean or maybe if
like other people
could make less or more it just depends on each individual really so it's it is
hard to put a
number on it to be honest can I just say one thing as well mm-hmm what I've
noticed is what
could be a lot of money to one person depending on like where we live how much
rent we pay could be
not like and I would just like my me saying this like say for instance me and
Jess she lives in
London she has a lot higher rent than me so what would be a good day to me
would wouldn't be
necessarily a good day to her because her algorithms are more than mine if that
makes sense
so like anyone could you know like a good like some some amounts of money are
more to some
London someone who's got less rent or higher rent or does that make sense yes
yeah yeah because
I'm averaging about 140 credits a day so that's got to go up really hasn't it
well to be honest I
don't really like to like say numbers because like Sam is just made the very
very valid point that
it does differ with everybody you know what I mean so yeah yeah and you're
adding cash on top of
that as well okay I think you're doing amazing with yeah I am yeah I think that
's pretty good if
you're consistently earning that every day mm-hmm I think that that's a figure
that you can build on
over time um because I mean just I'm trying to compare to myself I think like
in the early days
you know that might have been similar to that in the early days but now it's
been so many years
and I've got regulars that I've had for years and obviously it's quiet if like
don't go on for ages
I need to build it back up like anyone but personally I would think like I just
go on for an evening
and I would I would hope to make like a couple of hundred credits of an evening
so for the full day
you know I'd hope to be earning more than that really I started to get regular
people
you will recognise me and come on yeah yeah yeah and it's just such an
individual thing to each
person isn't it because it's too much so many variables like what is your niche
how many how many
clients do you have how many people do you appeal to like how how open is your
niche or closed or
what kind of people come and see you are they people that chat for a long long
time or are
they just like quick ones like there's so many factors aren't they like you
know but then that
also means there's so many things that you can try unlike at the times when you
're not earning
so much because there's so many factors it means there's so many things you can
change and try
and yeah so yeah yeah but I do think it's important when we're talking about
the confidence in this
job I do think you know and we try not to talk about money too much because you
know we don't
want to make people feel bad if they're not earning a certain amount and we don
't want to give false
hope or whatever but you know you can earn a few hundred credits a day on cam
you know you can do
that and you can sustainably do that yeah it takes a lot of hard work doesn't
it
yeah and I think as well like um Kay you know you've literally just gone
straight into this like
full-time you haven't even like done two or three weeks or a month yeah and you
're earning
consistently 100 to 150 every day plus other clients that are you know yeah
cash or whatever
clients which I think is amazing yeah they're both building up yeah they're
both building up
I want I'm sort of aiming for a thousand a week amazing yeah no that's what I
call what it should
be you know together yeah it's great to have your your own individual goals as
well you know like
yeah it's great for anyone to have even if it's 200 a thousand you know
whatever it is it's great
to have a goal I think to for you know if you're doing this full-time I think
you have to have your
goals and I don't think you need to think small either like with you know there
are people who
have just started like becoming a dom in their 30s or whatever and now they're
like earning
big bucks like you can and aim high can you with it yeah well last season I was
here and I've come
back and as soon as I put the advert in all the ones I saw last season are all
going oh you're
back you're back they're all zooming in to see me plus new ones and then they
'll come back and uh
and then I'm coming in between yeah great well you've obviously got you've got
like that magic thing
whatever it is you've got the touch the talk whatever so you know yeah business
like the things
then isn't it yeah what I'll blow today he made me laugh because he forgot his
glasses he had a
good time he forgot his glasses he come back and said I know I had a good time
but I thought I'd
gone blind
is there anything that anyone would say on the confidence to start there
because I know that
that's you know been been difficult for some people having the confidence to
get on cam
I mean I know that there's a few calls that I would say to go back and watch
especially the ones
that talk about self-worth and sex work and like calming confidence and stuff
and
because I think maybe we get into our heads a bit too much about how we're
supposed to look or you
know not feeling good enough but you know it's not like that is it it's not an
industry where you
need to look a certain way I could say a quick personal something that helped
me yeah go for it
literally for me it was just doing it and it sounds ridiculous but I just didn
't think about it
and I just like jumped on and at the beginning I was like in free mode saying
hi to every username
obviously I'd had a few drinks to that point it was like right at the beginning
I'd done some phone
sex in the past but for me it was because anxiety is always worse like thinking
about it is always
worse like most of the guys are complimentary and if you're really worried
about it don't go in
free because like at the end of the day if someone wants to be mean and pay you
then like that's a
bit different anyway but yeah I mean just go on and try it is probably the best
tip I could give
for like starting with confidence because you have to build the confidence with
CAM
as well as your own personal confidence so yeah thank you Catherine yeah yeah
that's really good
advice and yeah your confidence is it's not like build your confidence and then
start your confidence
builds like you say as you're coming that's certainly the same thing as you
realise what you
like like it's gonna be personal for everyone so you kind of just have to try
it and if you can't
get to the stage where you want to try it and like you can't do it then maybe
it's not for you
and like that's boundary but if you can just like log on and just try yeah and
like if you've
started on the phones like a couple of people have I mean if you've got
regulars that are on the
phones that you feel that you built a connection with then maybe that's a good
place to start like
telling them it's a good place to start and it's always good for when you're
not
feeling CAM like when you've got a rest in which phase or whatever like I have
today
yeah but yeah so so yeah that's my tip and like using the group as well like
you know like Catherine
there's so many lovely people in the group who are willing to like just lift
you up and I get so
many nice compliments it's crazy like even in free like when I'm like just
bored and I go in
free because I'm just like I don't want to wait I just like feel chatty I just
get so many people
just like oh I love the view I love your hair I love your lips I love your eyes
like literally
so many different compliments and it's always like oh god like that is like
surprising to be
getting so many compliments even if they're just coming in say like you're
gorgeous and then they
leave it does lift you up or it has for me for my experience and I was very
worried about it
um I can be quite an insecure person like um so I just did it and I actually
found that
what I did originally is I burnt myself out um and I did it for like two weeks
what really
addicted and then I stopped for a bit and then I rejoined with this agency and
then just took it
slower so don't like earning money can be really addictive so if it is going
well and you're
feeling really empowered try not to burn out too quick because that's how some
girls I think
last short amounts of times in this sort of job
yeah but yeah I'm in a mood now because I think that that's that's my point on
that
oh thank you for having me. I think I'll move on to the next point then shall I
?
Yeah for one okay so finding your niche and building your profile so um
obviously in the
beginning maybe people like you're not really going to know what your niche is
and that's fine
you can just experiment like Raul was saying earlier there's so many different
things you can do
on cam so you can experiment with whatever you feel comfortable with and then
see
you know how each thing feels to you and then build from there but when you
have got your niche
and you know what you're offering and you know what you like and what you don't
like
and you can start to build your profile around that so your profile you want it
to be unique
and individual to you and we can we can help with this and we've got so many
over training
videos that also help with building the profile and but yeah it's good to build
it around your
unique personality and your niche and this is really going to attract the
clients to you
and rather than just having something generic well you know I've seen some
profiles and
I think that they just copy and paste the same thing like because I've seen so
many profiles
that all look exactly the same so don't do that definitely don't do that and
I know that when you start with what your profile is very basic but we can help
you to build it up
and just really make it look amazing because this is what the client's going to
see before they see
you so you want it to be a reflection of you and you know it's amazing as
possible so you get
loads of them coming to you I think when you're a newbie as well it's fine for
it to be like
really really basic and terrible because they love newbies so obviously build
it up as you go
as you find your niche but I think like the most simple thing ever was when I
did the best when I
first started because it was like clear that I was such a newbie because I didn
't have like anything
to write also a lot of the guys don't read your profile first before coming
into your cam
just a little point but yeah building up the profile over time is definitely
good
yeah they do love newbies that's for sure and then yeah not all of them will
read it that's that's
true but some of them will because they'll tell you yeah definitely I think it
's I think it's more
just for if you've got a new profile I just think that maybe it's actually
better not to have it look
too professional because then you don't look like a newbie but obviously when
you've been on for
a while build it and build it but I think maybe right at the beginning it doesn
't matter if it's
like really short and sweet yeah exactly exactly so it all works out great you
know in the beginning
while you don't know what to write on there you don't have to write much anyway
because you know
but yeah actually in later slides we talk more about the profile so we'll get
back to that a
little bit later on yeah okay so the third point is to create the space and
basically invest in this
so if you're coming full time you want your space that you're coming in to be
like you're
it's basically where you're going to be spending most of your time really so
you want it to be
comfortable you want it to be and you know you want to look appealing to the
clients as well
and so yeah like if this is your full-time job or even if it isn't you know and
you've
you're able to I would definitely invest in making this space around you where
you're coming
and as nice as possible maybe you can come on the bed or on a couch and you
could have a stand
into your laptop and you can even get like a portable keyboard so you can prep
the laptop up
and you can lie on the bed or the couch or whatever it is and have your
portable keyboard so you
know having to be bent over the laptop and lighting is super important and so
yeah and just try and
create like a nice inviting in picture for the client to come to them. I think
if you've got like
a few places as well it can help to have a bit of variety when you've got like
longer term
clients if you're on quite often to not be in the same spot all the time like
sometimes I'll do this
this is like my from my client work really but sometimes I'll do this which is
literally
to the little corner of a house it looks like an office but it's not nice to be
in the picture
sometimes like cooking or whatever or on the sofa or upstairs because they feel
like they
get to know you a little bit then don't they yeah yeah yeah they like to see
parts of like they think
they're seeing more of your house and stuff so occasionally switching it up
also just sometimes
you might be more comfortable doing it somewhere else but having a setup that's
always set up for
full time is definitely really helpful in it yeah I think when you're thinking
the longer term and
when you're on more often it's about like it is like variety matters doesn't it
and like you're
thinking about the whole journey of the client who's like a regular client of
yours you're thinking
about like your relationship with them and how close they feel to you and how
excited they feel
by you your space is a part of that isn't it yeah for sure okay so outfits
props here and makeup
so this is something else that you can invest in when starting on cam so of
course if you've
got regular clients and you don't want to always be in the same outfit just as
much as you don't
want to be in the same space you want to be changing it up and so props when
thinking about props
think about what your webcam persona is what your niche is and you can get
props slash toys in
you know in that genre and you're here in makeup so also investing this as well
but
with with hair and makeup you can actually get like super cheap wigs I know
some of girls like
to use wigs on cam and especially ones who like to change their identity or
cover their identity
a little bit more and for makeup for calm I wouldn't wear expensive makeup on
calm I would just wear
the cheaper stuff because you know it's it's not the same as if you're wearing
it in real life like
you don't see it the same and you always put more on anyway and so yes that's a
little bit about that
and finally hd webcam and lighting I've probably said that a million times but
on all of these
rooms but it's super important and how you see me now I would not come with
this like this because
it doesn't look so great but usually I'll have a big ring light and having a
light in the front
and a light in the back actually works really well and and obviously the
quality of your webcam is
super important because at the end of the day they're paying to see you and if
they can't see you very
well then and then they're not going to stick around basically they're going to
find someone
who they can actually see so this one is super super important and okay then I
'll move on to the
next slide sorry it's just froze it's the moment oh there we go okay
are you going to do this one real or should I go through this one I can do yeah
okay okay
okay also got lovely Sami's profile there so keeping on top of your profile so
it's very
important to update your profile regularly when coming full time as it keeps
your regulars hooked
as it gets the new content from you it will also push your profile to the top
of searches so you're
more likely to be spotted by a new client yeah so this is something that you
should be doing
all the time really I mean it's something that I do each time I go on it's made
little tweaks and
things just because I know it pushes my profile up and I'm more likely to get
seen but if you're
doing it full time then you're getting a lot of information aren't you because
you you know as
as we said your confidence grows as you get to know what you're doing you know
your your niche grows
or develops or whatever so your profile grows and develops with all of those
things as well
because you get to you get to see like themes you know a few people will come
back and talk about
the same similar thing so then you'll be like oh that's that's a little story
or little tidbit or
something I'm interested in that can add to my profile so listening to your
regulars and like
what what it is they like about you and then making sure that that's
highlighted on your profile
and in your photos as well so yeah keeping on top of your profile is you know
regularly adding
photos and videos you know if you can if you can do a few different angles or
sort of you know
outfits or locations obviously we've got those the shoots that we offer a good
place to get some
pictures and so yeah uploading your content quite regularly will help you
profile
and your interview so yeah so your AdultWork interview so if you go to my
details and edit
profile you'll see that there's the AdultWork interview so it's like about 15
questions and just
making sure that that interview is filled in will bring you up in more more
people's searches so
that's really important that you do that and that's something that go in and
tweak sometimes as well
um my profile you know was sub for quite a long time is check my my like alter
egos change
loads of times but these days it's been switched for a long time but it's more
towards the dom side
now so I went and changed my interview and to make my answers a bit more on the
dom side um so yeah
as things change you can always change these things and update it and your bio
so obviously
your bio is the is the important bit isn't it that's where anyone that comes to
your profile is going
to get an instant you know message about who you are and what you like and you
know whether or not
they want to see you on page so you wanted to stand out you know you can use
the bb code
and we can show you how to do it or your mentor can show you if you're not sure
to make tabs and
to put things involved you can put little emojis on there and stuff um like we
've said before you
want it to be quite individual because there are loads of agencies who will
copy and paste profiles
and it's all just like big juicy ass big tits blah blah blah but that's not you
know that's not
really getting anyone's attention because it's the same as all the others so
having something that's
a bit personal making you know so that they know you're a real human because
they want to connect
with someone who's real um yeah so and and writing your bio for the client that
you want to attract
you know not just writing it because you think oh all guys want to hear this
sort of thing
thinking about the type of person that you want to attract that you can talk to
for a long time
and writing it as if you're writing your profile to them you know as if it's
like a you know an
interview you're writing to what you want to achieve on you manifesting so um
yeah it's important
to think about the language and you know how you come across in your bio um
your strap line
so yeah the strap line is the the only little bit of text isn't it that they
see just below your
picture when they're scrolling through all the girls so I change my strap line
every time I go on
or I try to uh might be the old time I don't but usually change it and then
usually that's
I'll put on my strap line a little bit of an invitation for something they
might want to
come and see so I'll mention something that I'm wearing or somewhere I've been
or something I'm
doing so they've got a little taster of what they're going to get when they
come in then I'm going
to tell them about or show them or whatever uh to try and entice them in um and
your price
per minute so yeah on your um webcam settings you can change your price per
minute so we set it as
the standard one but for anyone that's new starting but you know like any
business you look at inflation
you look at the trends you think about like what everyone else is doing and you
know if you're
business minded and you're doing this full-time this is something that you need
to be thinking
about what is your price per minute how many girls are online what's their
price per minute you know
sometimes it's a case of bringing it down so you get a load of calls in and
then putting it back up
you know I I know that when I get like two or three four good regulars I'll put
my prices up because
once they're hooked in enough that I know they're going to keep coming back I
'll put my prices up
because I know they're not really going to look I know they're coming back
anyway um yeah so playing
around with your price can can be really good thing to do especially if you're
full-time
um because you want to be treating it like a business don't you
um blogs um does anybody here do blogs already okay no just a reason I had it
in my head that I
thought Lauren I might have done a blog but maybe I'm thinking of somebody else
um
Logs is something that I have done a couple of blogs but not for years this is
something that I
did when I first began but again it's just another thing to add to your
character isn't it is to add
to your you know what you're selling is blogs you know and you can talk about
anything on there
can't you you can talk about experiences you've had or go through your typical
day or you better
shares or whatever it is that is you know appropriate for your niche um I guess
it's just
another way to grab people's attention isn't it and to get people engaging with
your profile as well
anything else on that one selling items actually selling items I'm not quite so
sure about this
one because they've taken how are they taking that off the profile recently
yeah you can't do that
anymore yeah unfortunately oh yeah it which also means your your one minute
though please go down
daddy go down to daddy then sorry girls one second okay go down to daddy um
your your wishlist
can't be as good now either because there's like five places to buy stuff from
yeah yeah that's a
bit of a bummer on the selling and and wishlist side um I did a wishlist the
other day for Kay
who was helping her with it and there was like hardly anything that I could
help her to put on
to the wishlist you know like used to be able to buy a jewellery or you know
like expensive items
they take that all the way so bit of a bummer yeah that's a real shame and it's
only something
that would notice was in the past week I was going I was going to get my
diamond stud earrings
and you used to be able to ask for that you used to have like lists of diamond
rings earrings
loads of stuff like that but it's all gone now nothing yeah yeah yeah I'm gonna
be because then
my daughter was running up and downstairs girl sorry thank you sammy yeah
selling
sell a lot of pictures and videos at least that's you know one that we can
still sell of them you
know you know it's not because yeah I used to sell all kind of you sell
pictures to them in your
private gallery so like I've set this up already for you
I know the none is in there as well now isn't it yes because somebody said to
me
tonight actually oh I love the hot none yeah I put it in there for you
not for all the none you've been there then thank you you're welcome I'll bless
you
um yeah and you're selling the dream I mean you're selling the dream aren't you
okay
and emails yes emails and feedback really important ones lorna is really good
at this like
replying to people's emails like I know that she'll just go on if she's not
been on
for a couple of days where there's a message everyone like and you can do quite
well
I get a little message from you saying you know I've just I've just messaged
everyone I've just sent
out all these messages and then she'll get another one saying how busy you are
I always I'm sorry I always email everyone back as well but you know with your
um what you said about
feedback for the past few times he was the feedback from like let's say two
weeks ago and I kept
leaving them positive feedback and he was saving it but it's not updating it at
all and he still
seems like that I haven't done it so I'm not really sure what's wrong okay that
's changed there is a
new it's because it used to be like instant with the feedback but they are they
do monitor it now
they do you know like with the photos and every user look through them
individually but I think
they do with the feedback now so it has to go to them for them to look at it
and then it gets
saying and I think it might be up to the member whether they choose to accept
it on some occasions
okay because it wasn't like all of them it was like few of them so I think it
was let's say about
two three weeks ago so he just asked me to leave it there's like a few of them
so I just clicked
positive positive positive and he said have you updated it you're happy and I
said yes
and then he keeps coming up like I haven't done it it's exactly the same names
exactly the same date
oh that's strange yeah maybe that has you like four times now yeah maybe that
is just a problem
with the site then or it could be his profile you know you know but um yeah
generally it takes a
little bit longer now than it used to it used to be instant because it has to
go back but but generally
it's a good way to to get people to come back isn't it and to build a
relationship with them
like see something a bit personal about what you've been talking about or that
you know that they
like so they'll come back um yeah so it's a good way to just keep keep that
relationship going
isn't it and building on it yeah but well done for doing it anyway well done
for doing all that
really bad because it takes time doesn't it yeah I always I always reply to all
the emails you know
and they usually do come in afterwards you know because it's the certain things
they ask and
scenarios they've got and all that yeah exactly and it's probably worth saying
as well not to spend loads of time on emails like because no yeah we'll just
want your time for free
and we'll send you really long ones so you know just giving them a nice reply
but keeping it quite
short and come and see me on cam you know so yeah this is basically I get like
would you do this
this is my scenario so they give you this entire thing and I say yes I would or
I wouldn't I just
usually say yes yes of course I'm all up for that and all that yeah yeah which
is perfect they're
perfect email won't they you know exactly what you what they want then that
fits you
thank you you're okay okay okay okay okay okay then shall we move on shall we
yes I think I think that I mean for the photos I probably should have said as
as well like because
if you're full time and you you you notice that you've gone a bit quiet that's
one good thing to
change isn't it that's one good thing to mix up like for your profile for your
main photos
they're really important aren't they they can really make a difference with how
many calls you
get just that one main photo yeah like I'll play around with it and I'll change
it to one that I
think is really good one and they'll go really quiet and then I'll change it to
another one which I'm
not even that fussed about and I'll be really busy so really good to just play
around with that
first photo and make sure like that one time he's gone there that it's that you
're quite close up
that you can see your face if if you're comfortable with that bit of your body
as well you know there's
not loads of extra stuff in the photo it's quite cropped and really important
with the photo
yes that photo is amazing it's like the perfect shot I feel so so nice and I
think that's probably
it probably is the most important thing on your on your whole profile because
that's ultimately
what they're looking at it decides if they're going to come with you or not so
um yeah getting
this right is very important and we can all help like you know with our advice
and we can all
if you're struggling of what want to pick you can just send us your options and
we can all decide
what we think is best with yeah um but yeah super important but I've also been
there too I've
changed my picture like yeah this is a hot picture and then it's like no holes
and then
a change on changing back to the one that always wins and I'm like oh yeah okay
okay just keep it
at that one so yeah getting that right and one last thing we should say about
the tick boxes
you know the tick boxes like underneath the picture on the right hand side like
the things
that you're into like obviously there's a long list of stuff and some of them
are pretty like extreme
but the more boxes you tick the more clients you're going to get because the
more searches
you're going to come up in obviously it doesn't mean that you have to do any of
those things
I mean this is just fantasy we're just talking about doing stuff so you can
tick I mean I think
I've got every single box ticked but you know I will still keep to my
boundaries and talk about
what I want to talk about but it's just widening the net isn't it the more the
more boxes that you
feel comfortable to take on that thing the better because the more people you
'll get coming in
yeah sure I had a new girl asked me actually about the boxes the other day she
said what does
this mean and it was about hard sports and I was like this one's quite
disgusting but like you know
some of the boxes are a bit out there but even if you got a tick like she said
you don't have to
do them you can just chat about it maybe okay then
sorry it's going super slow right now in my laptop I'm trying to change the
page but there we go
perfect so don't let come drive you let you drive come
so it's important to set your cam schedule and plan content days so obviously
if you're doing
this full time um it's got to you know set like set out like a week schedule
and
and stick to it as best as possible and because if not maybe you'll procrast
inate or maybe you'll
like Catherine said earlier maybe you'll do two more string will end up burnt
out
so whereas if you're setting yourself a schedule and also planning in rest in
that schedule too
then um I feel like you can't go wrong there um and also planning content days
I think is important
um so you could even just do this before you go online you know when you're all
done
when you've got your outfit on and you make a point on whatever else and you
can spend some
time taking some contents before you go online or while you're waiting for
calls on the quiet days
and because if you're doing this full time like we mentioned earlier it's good
to keep the profile
fresh with new content for your regulars and I'm just for you know just for all
of them in general
but especially irregulars because they're seeing you and your profile a lot it
's good to give them
something new and the more content you have the more we can sell it for and it
all just feeds back
into each other okay so don't forget to take a break so if you're coming full
time and let's say
you're going online for six hours in a day and instead of doing that six hours
all in one go
maybe like make a plan to break it up and as you could say you know what I'll
do two hours in the
morning I'll do four in the afternoon or something like that or you know
however you want to do it
but yeah always make sure to have a little break and obviously if it's busy
then well if it was
busy for me I would just power through and just like just go for it while it's
busy but after that
make sure you give yourself a moment to just have have a moment away from it
and come back to your
own energy and so yeah I think that's super important okay so keep track of
your busy time
frames and this was something I was doing at the start and even when I've had
time off when I come
back to where I still do this and I always like write I used to write what
times I would go online
so like say like 10 a.m to mid day or you know whatever time it was and I'd
always write how much
I made and I've done that for a month I've done it every single time I was
online for the month
and then I would look back through the month and see you know if the mornings
were better for me
if the evenings if the nights you know afternoon whatever it was and so yeah I
think that's a good
thing to do because then you see exactly when it's worth you going online
because maybe I'll say
I will actually going on a other night it doesn't seem to work for me so then
you know you know that
you don't have to do that in the future you can just focus your your efforts to
go on in the mornings
or vice versa and depending on your niche and who you're marketing to will also
depend on what
time frames you're going to be working and I remember I used to love the
daytime clients but
now I feel like I'm liking the nighttime clients a bit more because a little
bit more naughty
so I always be am so after midnight until about six a.m that's when I make the
most money
unfortunately every single time because it's yeah I don't know it's the freak
ier people and that
seems to be what I attract yeah totally I hear yeah um but yeah it's like it's
one of them if you
know that's your busy time then you know you can go on at them times and then
just allow yourself to
to like have a lay in or whatever else because you have been working through
the night
and so yes I think it's like definitely really different for each person isn't
it like a lot
of girls ask or what's the busiest time I don't I don't think there is one I
think it just completely
depends on you and what time that it works for you and if you're consistent
with that time I don't
think there is a well from my experience I don't think there is a busy time I
don't think any time
can be busy it depends on your personal clients and yeah who you're that you
have to learn like
george was saying about writing down what time she went on and then how busy
she was so she knew
her times that's kind of well I think it could be bitty for anyone at any time
yeah never know
it's so variable and that's that's why it's important when you see I was going
to say that's
on me thank you for saying that and when you see like people in the group
saying oh you know I'm
really really quiet at the moment it's important not to let that put you off
because there are you
know there are often people texting me saying oh well they're doing when
someone's not doing well
and vice versa and I've seen it myself like I've seen people posting they're
doing really great
and I've done shit and vice versa then the next day I'll do really well so not
judging by what other
people are doing definitely and I think staying consistent in your time frames
as well definitely
helps and I know one of our girls that's been with us now will sort of like the
longest time that's been
from the last one she's been with us like since the very start actually she
would always do the
same times I think it was like 11 till 1 a.m she'd just do two hours but she'd
do it every day
and she was absolutely killing it like she was always busy and it's because she
was just keeping
to those same time frames and clients knew when to find her and it's good to
build regulars isn't
it to be very consistent mm-hmm yeah I think that's so important daughter like
the time I know I know
not everyone could do that but if you are thinking of doing this full time I
think keeping as much as
you can and like letting it fit in with your life like you say don't it can
drive you you type can
like if you can just get a two-hour window but you could stick to that each day
that's a way to do
it like even if it's just two hours like you say like 11 to 1 or 9 to 11 or 2
till 4 or whatever
just if you could do those two hours every day I feel like really really works
massively yeah for
sure because you get the client like if you get clients that go on at the same
time so that'll
become your regulars so like they'll go on an everyday time at work or you'll
get the client
that go on at night time like you know once the wife is in bed as bad as us
sounds or whatever you
know like they go on at the same time so then if you're on in those times they
're going to be
regulars so even if you are only online for two three hours and but you're busy
that whole time
you could be making an absolute killing and I'm one thing as well actually if
you know what time
you're going to be on for the week write it on your profile so what you can
write is and my next
availability is then you'll have like a first day the 21st one till five Friday
the 22nd
four till five or you know whatever it is and literally write down what days
and what times you're
going to be on and then they have availability availability sort of positioning
dash camping now
in the broadcast so yeah and I always like when I log on put how long I'm gonna
stay on for I don't
know how that works but like you can do it in your profile if like gonna be
more consistent but if
you want to do it just in the moment just go on to that dash cam thing that's
like in the middle of
buttons on broadcaster I think it's dash cam yeah you can definitely use that
for sure um
but like you said that's more just each time you're logging on whereas yeah
yeah that's what I'm
saying like if if you can set much more specific times it's better to put it in
profile but like
that's what I do when I'm just like logging on a little bit more spontaneously
yeah for sure so
it's good to use both depending on what you know what what you can do like if
you don't know what
you're going to be on then use that one but as if you know if you've already
set your schedule
for the week and you know what you're going to times you're going to be on then
I would definitely
definitely write it on your profile because you know it's possible just try
everything really
I suppose I think it's about the important thing there like by you driving it
not letting it drive
you when it comes to times is that you're being intentional like anything in
life that you're
doing with intention it's very different to something that you're dipping in
and out of and
like or how do I feel today or getting distracted or like it's coming you know
it's not if you're
you want to manifest that your full time going to make this work intentionality
is like the most
important thing isn't it yeah definitely the intention but obviously we're all
different people
in the way of like how we work so some people work with a specific routine that
would work
and some people could do full time but they'll do it based on their like good
and bad physical
health days like someone like me or something like that like it is going to
work different for
everyone but definitely the intent of just like wanting to do it and that's
probably the best thing
but yeah like it can be at least for me it's different um for what times I go
on sometimes just
based on how I'm feeling but same for everyone of us
yeah for sure okay then so um like we mentioned before don't let slow days
get to you and look at the bigger picture so we actually was having a chat
about this recently
was on me Catherine and when we went through and had a look what you'd earned
in the last six weeks
I think it was popping up more than you actually thought and yeah well it's
been the last three
weeks that I will have earned like the most because that's when I've stopped
drinking and I've been
like on cam almost every day so six weeks would have been less but in three
weeks I don't know how
much I've made but quite a lot to me considering I took a big break yeah
amazing yeah like obviously
on the slow days you can start to especially in the beginning I think once you
've done it for a
while you don't feel like that anymore because you know it's going to pick back
up again and yeah
but especially in the beginning yeah you can have doubts and stuff but then if
you actually take
a step back and just even just look for your credit statement for the past
month you might shock
yourself from how much you've actually made because in that moment you're not
feeling that you just
feel on the moment of oh this is this is a slow day I'm not doing well you know
yeah so naps and downs
sort of business isn't it because of the variability like sometimes you're
going to feel a little bit
more deflated but like you know it will pick up again yeah slowy kind of yeah
and you just can't
let it back like but it's not like it gets louder because flow is natural
normal so it should be good
and I think like even you say that gee like after a while you don't worry as
much but I know that
sometimes even we have like a day where we're like oh a couple of days it's
quiet and we're like oh
my god like is this it now like so yeah I think those thoughts can creep in can
't they when you just
like you put the time aside and you're annoyed that you've not had a good day
but yeah always always
always comes back yeah it's always up and down definitely and like it's just
yeah like I said
it's just good to just let back and just look at it from a different
perspective like
see how well you've done in the past month or the past year or you know and
then it's like doesn't
feel so bad and taking action as well like because you can have like a quiet
couple of weeks
but if you know you know if it's gone on for more than like a few days you know
that you need to
take action you know you need to think about some of the points that we've
talked about your pictures
you profile there's other things that you need to try bidding or whatever so
that you know you're
you're actively working at it like a business and not just waiting for the good
day to come you know
yeah for sure and if you do all the things that we've mentioned and go through
all the
training then there's no reason why it shouldn't pick back up again because
yeah invest in like
like we've seen earlier about investing into this obviously I was speaking
about money like
investing in the setup but also investing your time into training yourself and
making your profile
look amazing and tweaking it and whatever else you know like the more time that
you invest in this
the more it's going to retain like the more you're going to do well you know
can I just add little tips that I've got as well to think that that was going
to
um say to Lorna earlier when she was messaged in the group one of the things as
well that I would
really advise anyone who's thinking of doing this full time is there's going to
be days that you're
going to do really really well there's going to be that day where you earn a
shit ton of money
and one of the things that I've learned is I will still then log on the next
day because it's
so easy to think oh fuck it I'll have three days off excuse my language sorry
but like you know like
I've got loads of money let's just have three or four days off like wow yeah
and I've done that
so many times and now like I've got that of yeah that's amazing and we're
celebrating like right
in the group or you know we're all going to celebrate for you but still log on
the next day for them
two hours that you're sticking to because that's what your clients want and
then they'll keep coming
back and coming back and they'll know that like they might have spent two three
four hundred
quid review the night before but then you're still back the next day and I
think that's quite
important you know like that because it's so easy to think half a load of money
today it outweighs
all the bad days let's just go and like have three or four days off and that's
just my personal
tip of still do the next two hours like the two hours the next day or yeah no
like you don't do
six but still log in then two or three or four hours that you're that you've
written on your
profile you know like because your clients will see that your regulars will see
that and think
oh wow spent a lot of money with her yesterday but she's still back today she
wants more you know like
I think that's something that I've learned through my journey of coming
not spending all the money straight away if you have a really good day not
spending
it all and then you're like oh ship and you have a quiet day back to square one
yeah yeah if you're
all-time you need to think full-time don't you and be putting money aside not
just splashing when
the good days are good yeah which is hard yeah I still want your heart now oh I
'm like whoa but
like now I've got that I will still love on the next day or whenever I've like
scheduled to if you
know what I mean sometimes I still spend too much money though but you know
yeah great advice thank you so many okay
so now we have some extra tips
okay do you want me to um yeah sure okay
a divider okay okay all right um so the clients want a connection to be held in
a safe space to
explore their fantasies uh without judgment right down points about each client
this will
give the opportunity to get returning clients so yeah yeah getting to know your
clients basically
isn't it you know being curious about them listening not feeling like you know
how the session is
gonna go before you even started it you know it's just being open and curious
about because most
of the time they're it's so easy like they'll tell you exactly what they want
you know and you can
some with some regulars you can do the same scenario over and like I've been
talking about the
same scenario about what we're gonna meet with some guys for like five years so
yeah the more that
you can get to know and give them a space to just develop their own fantasy
with you the more that
they're gonna come back um having a little notebook just to write down I mean I
'm so I get
caught up with this still now all the time like clients will come and be like
blah blah blah oh
you don't remember me do you and I'm like oh fucking like you can be one of a
million guys I literally
have no idea but I have to go play along with it so yeah if I if I know I've
got a guy that I've
been talking to for a long time I'm like yeah I need to this is important that
I need to remember
his username a key couple of points about him you know make him feel special
that he's the only
one that I really enjoy chatting with because they all think that so yeah the
more that you make them
feel special or however they want to feel they might not want to feel special
they might want to
feel degraded the more that you can make them feel the way they want to feel
and remember that for
next time you know they're more likely they are to come back um what else have
we got yeah just
what I was saying already really be curious and open I think that's it's just
it's difficult isn't
it when you're not feeling so confident maybe you haven't really found your
niche yet and you know
you're maybe you have a couple of guys who just are souls and then you're like
oh no so you're trying
to like you try and desperately to be the person that you think they want you
to be
whereas you know it's much better to just slow it down be a blank canvas so
they you know they
just reflect back to them what they're giving to you that's what they want they
want a safe space
where you can just reflect back to them and be you know this safe curious
person that's you know
interested in them interested in what they're interested in and even if you don
't know about it
you know asking them to tell you about it um so yeah just stay in opening
curious for your clients
um knowing your audience so yeah obviously it's really important or a good
skill to be able to
determine whether somebody might become a regular or whether they're one-stop
customers you don't
want to be spending a load of time on somebody who's just trying to rush
through the process and
obviously just wants you know a quick thing um you don't want to give away
things too soon
you know everyone's got different boundaries but if somebody's coming in your
chat and getting
naked you know you know that that's not a customer who's got much money and it
's probably not worth
the investment if that's the case so yeah no I suppose as you go along you get
to know which
type of customers are going to come back and keep spending money with you and
which ones you know
they might be great customers for one night but they're only going to be for
that one night so
you need to ex you spend your energy wisely don't you and make sure that you're
spending
on the people that are going to be long term um yeah yeah engage engage engage
again a lot of
comes into my head here because she's so good at this um that if you are so
good at this you
inspire thank you speak to everyone yeah so just engage your clients in any way
that you can whether
it's messages or feedback or whatever it is just engaging them to get them to
notice it on come back
and talk to you um have your client do things in their day-to-day life to make
them think of you
so yeah I mean the more that you can get them thinking about you in between
your calm sessions
then better and it used to be a lot easier because you used to be able to give
out like email
addresses and like you know speak to them in between and get them to come
online it's a lot
harder now because obviously people can do you can do in text messages I
suppose now so you can
text them at least yeah yeah so if you've got all the services there on your
profile which
hopefully if you're full-time you want to be thinking about adding those extra
services if you can
um then yeah then you can be then you can be engaging them in between calm
sessions in that way
um and yeah getting them to do things in their day-to-day life I mean this is a
good one for
subs isn't it I mean if you're a dumb on cam it's good to you know be setting
your sub tasks
that they can come back and tell you about and any even if it's not a sub
client if you can say
something or even if it's not about what they're going to do in between your
session you can give
them a teaser about something that's going to happen with you in between your
session like I'll say
yeah I've got this hot girl coming around because like sometimes I dumb girls
and I've got this hot
girl coming around on Thursday because I know this client always speaks you
know is likely to be there
on a Friday so it's let he'll come back and ask me about what's happened that
week um so yeah any
little hooks that you can get to get them thinking about you in between the
session is a good thing
um set candidates with your client that's a cute one I think you added that don
't you Jay
yeah so yeah I I actually get quite into it sometimes when I have a new client
whenever new regular I'm really enjoying talking to so this is something that I
might do you know
work out when you're next going to see each other and I mean it can be part of
your little
secret relationship kind of that nobody else knows about it can be like a fun
little thing that you
know when when you're gonna come back and see me next like I can't wait to come
with you again
I'm gonna be you know here at this time and this time and I'll I'll be waiting
to see that you're
online and so yeah set candidates with your clients there's a cute one good way
to keep them
engaged um and like we said techs and phone calls to stay connected yeah if you
're full time then
you know you want to be utilising the site as much as possible really don't you
these are good things yeah it's huge chance to come
anything else in that one oh that's it for that one okay and that brings us to
the end
do we have any questions darlings
you know when you go full time do you tell the fact man what we earn
yeah I think it's the words to tell them oh no sorry we don't tell them yeah
that's up to you
right good yeah yeah so you you tell them I mean we we can we can help you like
to
guide you in the direction of yeah and we've got a call on that actually have
we got a call
still on that what is that was that one I'm not sure if that one was lost
because we've got a finance call where we went through all the stuff about
being self-employed
and all that but I'm not sure whether it's on there anymore because we lost a
few of our calls
and I don't want to know I don't want to know anything about being self-
employed
okay well maybe that's actually now I'm thinking about it that's cool that we
can do again because
when you're obviously when you're doing it full time you know it's a
consideration isn't it that
you're that you're self-employed and that you know you need to think about that
side of things so
maybe that's a call that we can do soon j to talk about like and stuff just
checking if it's on the
website I don't remember if this one was lost or not but um yeah if it was lost
we'll definitely
redo it and maybe even if it wasn't we'll still do something to touch on it but
yeah declare all
that yourself and as it's going for you bank I think it's definitely worth
doing it I mean
we've cashed it's different for sure depends on what you want to do but with
the come it goes
paid into your bank of course so yeah you don't want to be in you don't want to
be messing around and
you know and getting done for tax fraud and whatnot like not any taxes so um
yeah we recommend
like you don't let the tax man know for sure and about how to do the taxes
online and there's help
clients and like you can get an accountant as well which will do it all for you
so there are ways
of making like the self-employment easier yeah I I do that I have an accountant
which is like
300 quid or something but I just know that everything's sorted and I don't have
to do anything
so it's not earning enough it's well worth it to get an accountant because like
they they add in
things that like you couldn't possibly figure out without having the knowledge
like to take money
off so yeah as well that's that's that's a point that we haven't mentioned
really which is quite
important isn't it like if you can like all the hard brand bill he likes you
know like if you're
working from home all of those things can have bits being deducted and the
accountant do that but
I don't do that when I do mine because I don't earn enough yet so I don't need
to worry about it but
an accountant knows how to do that stuff already so when you're earning enough
money it's probably
a good idea to get an accountant unless you already have that knowledge
yourself
yeah so just being mindful if you are coming full-time of all the things that
you can expense
because you can obviously expense you know your beauty stuff you can expense
your outfit
you know any cam anything to do with your cam set up lighting whatever
I know exactly and obviously make sure as soon as you start camming to register
self-employed
if you're not already because uh yeah then oh like it's benefits fraud
otherwise isn't it yeah
yeah benefit fraud what's benefit fraud like when you're claiming benefits that
you don't deserve
so if you're earning should be taxed but you're not paying now you're not
claiming it like when you
do cash in hand jobs as such and you don't pay tax yeah I'm not on benefit so
it don't matter
no no it doesn't matter but if you're calming yourself employed so you need to
register as
self-employed I mean it's up to you whatever you do with your life but in a
legal sense
in a legal sense you want more like information because I'm not like you know I
don't know everything
but I just never been legal in my life that's fine then you you do you I have
no judgment
it doesn't happen if anyone needs that advice with that type of thing you know
we're not
actually but we do it ourselves so we're really happy to help you you know ask
questions if you
think about it just you know just think about it anyway at least I'm an old-day
pensioner love
probably be fine then so don't worry about it but I just wanted to throw the
tip out there for
anyone that didn't know about and wanted to do it because if does anybody else
have any questions
or anything else that they'd like to add
no no more questions just kind of think I only learned about the tips this week
oh yes I didn't know that oh okay and now how do you manage to get any tips oh
yeah the first
too nice well done yeah you don't need to trip I need to know all the tips like
that
you should probably you should go back through the website k and have a look at
some about old calls because some of them were absolutely ages ago but there's
a lot of good stuff
on there yeah little tips and things even if you just take one little tip from
like you know
listen a bit well that was a good one you know it put an extra 10 yeah so a
five of each client
yeah yeah it's a great if you can get them and how and how rude can you go on
your pictures
because yeah so yeah I had the guidelines of pictures so there's certain
guidelines that we
I had a friend over and we'd done some really rude ones because it follows the
guidelines anything
anything I know I've got them what's the guideline um sammy will send you sammy
spot with this
going to push me and don't throw your face is that guy
let's just be asked to come and we'll go through it yeah
like that I think mine might be too raunchy especially the uh food ones well I
mean I can try and find
it but if not I know sammy gave it to me before so maybe sammy can send you
that yeah we'll work
out yes yeah you'll work it out don't worry because they're very rude just you
're just kinky I love it
have you ever seen a fanny eat a banana
we it's no but I want to
fanny chopped it in half my friend couldn't believe it
what a great way to end the call I just had a very quick question is that okay
of course it's a bit
of a personal one um but we're saying like earlier about trying to get on every
day um and
I just wondered what people's experiences were doing that when it's like the
time of the month
the kind of thing because that's what I was trying to struggle to know like how
to
go about it um I think in my day I know that you just go through the blood and
do period play
but you could still go on with the pad and just not show the blood I think that
's the guidelines for
that we don't know you don't you don't have to play every time you know you don
't know I always say
that's how I always say sometimes I don't do anything and I am loads of money
it's fairies
in my day I want to tell the sea sponge up there
well that's what I was going to say so there are lots of people you know there
are lots of people
me included that don't really don't really do that don't really play on cam don
't get that
opportunity because you know it's all about the chat so you don't have to do
that by any means
in order to earn money even if you full-time you don't need to do you don't
have to if you don't
want to but obviously you don't want to do that I've got to take my way to um
because I can every
time my mummy period because I had this weird like couple of months where I was
on more than I was
at half so obviously I had to I think if you distract them away from every
figure so it's like I'd
get like how can you do pussy play or do this or do that whatever of course be
let's get me wet first
what you think you know both weird you want to touch which is really boobs and
then if you just
carry on doing that and just do like that they don't normally don't last or don
't even think to say
oh I'm on a minute I asked for a pussy play like ten minutes ago I've gone on
before in a sort of
black sexy style adult nappy and pulled my trousers down and no one said the
thing got
put off had a problem and it wasn't even like a baby plaything I was just like
sorry I'm on my
period no one even cared oh yeah I I admitted so if it's a regular and the like
oh can you do this
again like he'd done like last week I'm just like well I can but you'll see
things so you could
sometimes turn it into a fetch thing for a week or whatever or if you use tamp
ons if you talk
the string like it's probably going to sound like something backwards I might
to stick tampons or
anything in them do though that's I think the thing with eevee um what I was
going to say it wasn't
packaging what I was going to say was about sponges so I use sponges quite a
lot I I go
sex parties and things and I'm wearing full on my period and there's you cannot
tell at all
really comfortable like I absolutely love them I used to work with them so you
can't stop working
can you we used to have a slap a day sponge up there and then dig it out
afterwards yeah
yeah we can get you just search on google for soft tampons that's what they're
called soft tampons
they kind of use them in spain all the time um they're a bit pricey they're
about pound each
it would work for you and just try if not then just as I said just don't do too
much bottom stuff
on your period people still want stuff like lots of people just want boobs or
chat like I do different
things every time so it's never it's never like always I've got a niche but I
do completely
different cam sessions like sometimes I'm naked fully getting fucked sometimes
I'm just like
talking not naked at all for hours like it doesn't like it's only about how you
feel on your period
that it's going to really affect your cam but I don't think you should let your
period affect your
cam if you want to go on but then also I mean if you are full time and you know
that there's a
few days a month where you're going to be bleeding you know that could be a
factor that into your
work can't you it's part of the beauty of this job is that it's not capitalist
that you know we're not living in that frame we can live you know in accordance
with our bodies
you know that's kind of the beauty of it is that we are living in accordance
with our
own schedule it's part of the flow isn't it like the feminine flow and the cam
work and all that
stuff yeah I hope that's helped ebay thank you thank you um and it's it's a
good chance maybe to
expand your like skills and stuff you know like um the fantasy writing
workshops stuff like that
maybe you know it's something the way you can just expand your skills for like
non-playing
sessions and to try and draw them out a bit so you feel a bit more comfortable
um because I think
we can get drawn into play very quickly can't we if we're feeling a bit self-
conscious or not
not so sure about the sessions yeah definitely so I just had one thing in this
well if you are
feeling a bit you know I do this when I've just not always be from on my period
if I'm just
feeling a bit groggy but I still want to log in I just do I end so you they can
't see you at all
there's just instant messages it's not as busy and obviously you can't charge
as much money but
if you've got regulars by then yeah yeah I can find that that's a good little
yeah there's different options like phone chat as well so you don't always have
to go on can
yeah yeah that's a good idea thank you so many that was good advice yeah thank
you
thank you you would be question anybody else before we finish up
no real good well it was lovely to see you ladies really good to see you we've
got um the call on
sunday isn't it on sunday morning so for anyone that fancies it's just the the
mental health
checking call so it just be nice casual you want for us to get together and
have a bit of a chat
I might even do it from bed it sounds good so yeah hopefully I'll see some of
you there
and don't be nice to see you all and talk to you all yeah lovely to see you
everybody
hope you have a good rest of the night bye guys